scfb.io 2017-08-15

# Privacy – StellaService

## PRIVACY POLICY

**StellaService  Inc. Privacy Policy**

StellaService Inc. (the “Company,” “we” or “us”) is committed to ensuring the integrity of its business and customers by providing those who use or visit our Internet Web sites with a safe and secure Internet environment that respects and protects their personal privacy. The following privacy policy is in effect for every Web site maintained or operated by the Company, and we ask you to read it thoroughly.

**Our Pledge**

We will not release any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically instructed us to release such information or have consented to our doing so. You give consent for the Company to disclose your personally identifiable information if such disclosure is needed to provide services you have expressly requested, or if we believe disclosure is necessary under one of the exceptions discussed below.  
We have provided mechanisms below for you to communicate your privacy questions and concerns, and we will make a reasonable effort to respond to them.

**Your Consent**

By using the services provided to you through the Company’s Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, but all changes will be posted to this page so that you can remain informed as to what information we collect and how we use it. Changes are effective when posted to this page, and your continued use after any change is posted is an acceptance of the change.

**Helpful Definitions**

“Personally identifiable information” is information-such as name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address, financial information, purchasing habits and other types of information that can be used to uniquely identify a user.  
“Anonymous Information” is information that does not personally identify you. This includes information on how you use the Company’s Web site (such as places visited and search queries performed). Anonymous information also includes the domain names and/or I.P. addresses (as explained in greater detail below) of browsers that visit the Company’s Web site, time of day the site was visited, and other non-personally identifiable information. Anonymous information is information that is not tied to any individual.  
COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

**Registration**

You can visit the Company’s Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself to us. It is only when you wish to receive or purchase additional goods or services that we may require you to register with us by providing certain personally identifiable information, to select a user name and password, and to agree to our Terms of Use. The Company will use this information to:

• Welcome you to the Web site.

• Send communications to you about the Web site, including new features and services available through the Web site.

• Share your information with affiliates, and allow them to contact you directly, if you have consented to this beforehand.

• Verify your qualifications for receiving goods or services we offer over the Web site or for other programs or activities.

If you indicate to us that you do not want to receive certain types of communications at the time of registration, we will respect your wishes, and comply with your preferences, however there may be cases where this will limit the Web site services available to you.  
Sharing Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties

If we share Personally Identifiable information with third parties, with your prior consent, they may use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people without your consent.

PLEASE NOTE: In certain special cases, we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with the Company’s rights, property or operations, other Web site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

If you provide feedback or an invoice number or other information with respect to an evaluation of a business, you consent to us sharing such information and your personally identifiable information with such business.

**Anonymous Information**

When you use the Web site, we may collect anonymous information, even if you have not registered with the Company as a customer or entered into a Terms of Use Agreement. We may use this information to examine how the Web site is used or to help the Company improve the services it offers. The Company will not share anonymous information with third parties if we know that this anonymous information will be linked by third parties with personally identifiable information of yours obtained from another source, unless we have given you notice and you have given us authorization to do so.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are harmless bits of code that an Internet site assigns to your browser to keep track of who you are when you use a Web site. There is no risk of the information on your hard drive being exposed to the outside world since a web site can only read the cookies it creates.

Cookies are sometimes used on the Internet to improve the delivery of services to users by enabling the Web site to “customize” the particular services or information offered to each user.

The Company may employ or use cookies from time to time. You have a choice as to whether you want to participate in the use of cookies before they are used by adjusting your browser settings. Third parties, however, may have their own policies about the use or cookies, and the Company does not have control over these practices. You are responsible for obtaining information about cookies on third party Web sites if you believe this is important to know.

As a general rule, you can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features will not work as intended.

**Use of IP Address**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a set of numbers that is assigned to your computer. Web servers – the powerful computers that provide web pages for viewing – automatically identify your computer by the IP address assigned to it during your session online.

The Company may collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to monitor and audit the use of the Web site. We can and will use IP addresses to identify users of the Web site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Company’s terms of use or terms of service, or to protect our service, site, or other users. We will not share or sell linked user behavior and personal user information with any third parties unless you have given us authorization to do so.

PLEASE NOTE: Under certain circumstances, IP addresses and/or domain names may be linked to personally identifiable information, when said information is stored in databases managed by Internet registrars or registries such as Network Solutions.

**Third Party Relationships**

WEB SITES THAT ARE OPERATED OR MAINTAINED BY THIRD PARTIES ARE NOT COVERED BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY. Whenever you authorize the Company to share information about you with third parties, you are responsible for determining whether the third party employs an acceptable privacy policy. The Company does not automatically make this determination for you, and does not warrant that any particular third party maintains a privacy policy that is acceptable to you. Also, when you exit our Web site to link to a Web site maintained by a third party, the Company has no control over the operation of that Web site or the integrity or safety of any information you may provide to them.

**Security**

The Company operates secure data networks protected by industry standard procedures, to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control.

Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. For example, we impose strict rules on employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur; we will make every effort (such as the use of employee passwords and non-disclosure agreements) to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

**Contacting Us**

If you have questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, please contact:

StellaService 75 Broad Street, Suite 1010 New York, NY 10004 (212) 366-1483
